Tufts College Alumni Bulletin UP010
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts College Alumni Bulletin
1927 -- 1943
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Alumni Relations
Tufts University Alumni Association
UP010
4 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of bound issues of the The Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, from 1927 through 1943. The Bulletin was more directly concerned with alumni activities and news than its predecessor, the "Graduate." The Bulletin reported births, deaths, engagements, marriages and other events in the lives of Tufts graduates. News was limited to reporting and advertising alumni events, and events on campus that might be of interest to alumni. The Bulletin also begins, for the first time, to report athletic schedules and scores of athletic contests.
The Alumni Bulletin replaced the Tufts College Graduate as the magazine for alumni in 1927. The Bulletin was printed in a small newspaper format on heavy newsprint until 1940 when it switched to glossy paper and a 6" x 4" size. The Bulletin was replaced by a new alumni magazine, "Tufts Topics," in 1943.
Related Materials
UP002, Tufts College Graduate, DCA.
- Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1927 -- 1943; UP010.001; 4 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This collection consists of bound issues of the The Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, from 1927 through 1943. The Bulletin was more directly concerned with alumni activities and news than its predecessor, the "Graduate." The Bulletin reported births, deaths, engagements, marriages and other events in the lives of Tufts graduates. News was limited to reporting and advertising alumni events, and events on campus that might be of interest to alumni. The Bulletin also begins, for the first time, to report athletic schedules and scores of athletic contests.
  The Alumni Bulletin replaced the Tufts College Graduate as the magazine for alumni in 1927. The Bulletin was printed in a small newspaper format on heavy newsprint until 1940 when it switched to glossy paper and a 6" x 4" size. The Bulletin was replaced by a new alumni magazine, "Tufts Topics," in 1943.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1927-10; UP010.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1927-12; UP010.001.001.00002 (Box Volume 1)
    [Alumni] Tufts men and the flood (reconstruction work after the flood)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1928-02; UP010.001.001.00003 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1928-04; UP010.001.001.00004 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1928-05; UP010.001.001.00005 (Box Volume 1)
    Alumnae Dramatic Club; Alumni day
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1928-10; UP010.001.001.00006 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1928-12; UP010.001.001.00007 (Box Volume 1)
    Alumnae Dramatic Club
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1929-02; UP010.001.001.00008 (Box Volume 1)
    Alumni trustees
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1929-03; UP010.001.001.00009 (Box Volume 1)
    Abbott, Porter S. (1914) married June 26, 1928, to Theresa E. Metz at Elizabeth, W. Va.
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1929-05; UP010.001.001.00010 (Box Volume 1)
    Alumni day
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1929-10; UP010.001.001.00011 (Box Volume 1)
    Alumni association meetings
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1929-12; UP010.001.001.00012 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1930-02; UP010.001.001.00013 (Box Volume 1)
    [Alumnae Hall] plans announced, to be named for Ruth Capen Farmer; Nomination of alumni trustees
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1930-04; UP010.001.001.00014 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1930-05; UP010.001.001.00015 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1930-10; UP010.001.001.00016 (Box Volume 1)
    [Alumnae Hall] Fundraising; Alumni association activities
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1930-12; UP010.001.001.00017 (Box Volume 1)
    [Alumnae Hall] Fundraising
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1931-02; UP010.001.001.00018 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1931-04; UP010.001.001.00019 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1931-05; UP010.001.001.00020 (Box Volume 1)
    Abbott, Rev. Lawrence (1929) married to Margaret W. Belden (1931) at West Hartford, Conn; Alumni day
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1931-10; UP010.001.002.00001 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1931-12; UP010.001.002.00002 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1932-02; UP010.001.002.00003 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1932-04; UP010.001.002.00004 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1932-05; UP010.001.002.00005 (Box Volume 2)
    [Alumnae Hall] Fundraising; Alumni day
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1932-10; UP010.001.002.00006 (Box Volume 2)
    Adams, Irene Nancy (1933) married Sept. 3, 1932, to Francis E. Butler (1931) at Quincy, Mass. p. 15.
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1932-12; UP010.001.002.00007 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1933-02; UP010.001.002.00008 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1933-04; UP010.001.002.00009 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1933-05; UP010.001.002.00010 (Box Volume 2)
    Judge Robert W. Hill, tomorrow's alumni; Alumni association meetings changes in constitution; Alumni day
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1933-10; UP010.001.002.00011 (Box Volume 2)
    Dr. Clarence E. Allen (D 1928) Married 5/20/33 to Eleanor M. Groder at Gardiner, Maine; Alumni association meetings
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1933-12; UP010.001.002.00012 (Box Volume 2)
    Dr. William S. Altman [M1927] married Sept 4, 1933 to Esther Kimball; Alumni association meetings
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1934-02; UP010.001.002.00013 (Box Volume 2)
    Alumni council
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1934-04; UP010.001.002.00014 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1934-05; UP010.001.002.00015 (Box Volume 2)
    Alumni day; Alumni trustees
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1934-10; UP010.001.002.00016 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1934-12; UP010.001.002.00017 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1935-02; UP010.001.002.00018 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1935-04; UP010.001.002.00019 (Box Volume 2)
    Dr. John L. Ahern Jr. Death of, 1934; [Alumnae Hall] Fundraising; Alumni council
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1935-05; UP010.001.002.00020 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1935-10; UP010.001.002.00021 (Box Volume 2)
    [Alumni day] Excerpt from adddress of President Cousens, "Objectives of Higher Education"; Alumni council
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1935-12; UP010.001.002.00022 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1936-02; UP010.001.002.00023 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1936-04; UP010.001.002.00024 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1936-05; UP010.001.002.00025 (Box Volume 2)
    John Holmes, Alumni day comes once a year
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1936-10; UP010.001.003.00001 (Box Volume 3)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1936-12; UP010.001.003.00002 (Box Volume 3)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1937-02; UP010.001.003.00003 (Box Volume 3)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1937-04; UP010.001.003.00004 (Box Volume 3)
    Alumni institute; Alfred E. Allen Jr. (1935) Married 3/25/37 to Marjorie E. Johnson (J36) at Wallingford, Conn; Alumni day
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1937-10; UP010.001.003.00005 (Box Volume 3)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1937-12; UP010.001.003.00006 (Box Volume 3)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1938-02; UP010.001.003.00007 (Box Volume 3)
    Adams, Robert G. (1930) married January 2, 1938 to Dolphie Bert (J30) at Tufts College. p. 14. Death of (9/29/37) Charles Rollin Allen Jr. (E1899).
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1938-05; UP010.001.003.00008 (Box Volume 3)
    Alumni institute; Alumni day; Death of (12/3/1937) Dr. Marion L. Albro (M1907); [Alumni association] Alumni 'promoted'; Alumni council
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1938-10; UP010.001.003.00009 (Box Volume 3)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1938-12; UP010.001.003.00010 (Box Volume 3)
    Nominations for alumni trustees
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1939-02; UP010.001.003.00011 (Box Volume 3)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1939-05; UP010.001.003.00012 (Box Volume 3)
    Alumni council; Alumni day celebration
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1939-10; UP010.001.003.00013 (Box Volume 3)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1939-12; UP010.001.003.00014 (Box Volume 3)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1940-02; UP010.001.003.00015 (Box Volume 3)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1940-05; UP010.001.003.00016 (Box Volume 3)
    Alumni council; Alumni day
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1940-10; UP010.001.004.00001 (Box Volume 4)
    Death of (6/9/39) Dr. Carl E. Allison (M1914). Alpha Omega Alpha Medical School granted charter.
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1940-12; UP010.001.004.00002 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1941-02; UP010.001.004.00003 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1941-05; UP010.001.004.00004 (Box Volume 4)
    Alumni day; Dick Skuse, Tufts Alumni Varsity Club
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1941-10; UP010.001.004.00005 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1941-12; UP010.001.004.00006 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1942-02; UP010.001.004.00007 (Box Volume 4)
    Muriel Allen (J 1941) Married 2/7/42 to Ransom Long (1971); Alumni day
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1942-05; UP010.001.004.00008 (Box Volume 4)
    Christine Alley (1943) Married January 1941 to Ronald Berry; Alumni council
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1942-10; UP010.001.004.00009 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1942-12; UP010.001.004.00010 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1943-02; UP010.001.004.00013 (Box Volume 4)
    Dr. Lione L. Albert (M 1912) Death of, Sept. 6, 1942.
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1943-05; UP010.001.004.00014 (Box Volume 4)
    Adams, Dr. Frank D. (H1914) Death of, Dec. 29, 1942. p. 16. [Lt. Maurice F. Ahearn [1942] (Marine Corps)] Cited for outstanding performance of duty on Guadalcanal, August 21, 1942, by Admiral William F. Halsey. Dr. Edward C. Allen (M 1939) Married 2/6/1943 to Barbara R. Daniels at Melrose MA. Death of (1/21/43) Rev. Pliny A. Allen (R 1901).